ggontemall.com 2019-01-27

# Privacy Notice : ggontemall.com, Your online shopping store

Our store online respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. To better protect your privacy, we provide the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.  
Personally Identifiable Information   
We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g. name, address, telephone number and e-mail address), also referred to herein as "personal information," unless you provide it to us voluntarily.

Age Requirement   
We do not sell or ship any items to anyone who is under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any personal information to us and reply on a parent or guardian to assist you.  
What We May Do With Personally Identifiable Information  
If you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we may use it to improve our understanding of your interests and concerns. We will also use this information to process your order.

If you tell us you would like to receive additional information from us by e-mail, we may use your information to occasionally contact you about changes to our website, new products, site and service updates and special offers which we think you¡¯ll find valuable. If you would rather not receive these e-mails, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions on the e-mail that you have received.  
Registration Information  
Our Site contains areas where you can submit information to us (such as our registration service), and we also have features (such as cookies and performance tracking technology) that automatically collects information from the visitors to our Site. During the registration process, you must provide us with a member name and password, your name, address and a valid email address. It is your responsibility to keep your password strictly confidential.

How We Protect Your Personal Information  
We store your personal information on a secure server and use procedures designed to protect the personal information we collect from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. Although we will take (and require our third-party providers to take) commercially reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected and stored on the Site, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored in our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

Cookies   
We may deposit "cookies" in your computer in order to identify you. Cookies are small data text files that are sent from a server computer during a browsing session. Cookies are typically stored on the computer's hard drive and are used by web-sites to simulate a continuous connection to the site. Security measures have been employed to prevent unauthorized access to visitor data. However, visitors acknowledge that our store does not control the transfer of data over telecommunication facilities including the Internet. Therefore, our store will not be responsible for any breach of security or the unauthorized disclosure or use of any such data on the Internet. You may configure your browser to reject cookies.

Notices  
We may send notices to you with respect to your use of the Site by sending an email message to the email address listed in your Account Information, by sending a letter via mail to the contact address listed in your Account Information or by posting a note on the Site when you access your account. You agree that we may provide notice to you through such means. Unless otherwise stated in the notices, the notices will become effective immediately.

Changes to this Privacy Policy   
Our privacy practices will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customer¡¯s needs. As we update and diversify our services our Privacy Policy may evolve. Please check this page for updates periodically. Please note: by using or registering with our Site or by providing personal information, you agree to abide by the applicable terms of our Privacy Policy.

Use of Site Signifies Consent   
By visiting this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy with respect to non-personally identifiable information. By providing personally identifiable information through the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy with respect to personally identifiable information. If you do not agree with anything described in this Privacy Policy, you may discontinue use of the website. Your continued use of any portion of the website following posting of changes to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of these changes.

General Contact Information  
For questions regarding our products or this Site, please contact us.
